linktub.com 2015-03-17

# LinkTub

##### Privacy and Data Security

At Linktub.com.com, your right to privacy and data security is a primary concern. That's why, when you visit Linktub.com.com, we help you maintain control over your personal data on the Internet. Below are the guidelines we use for protecting the information you provide us during a visit to our site or when you use our online support offerings.

##### Information We Collect

We may ask you to provide personal information when you:   
• Use our website   
• Request quotes, services, support, or information   
• Place orders for products or services   
• Subscribe to newsletters, promotional emails, saved cart reminders, or other materials   
• Apply for a job, submit your resume/CV, or create a candidate profile   
• Contact us   
Information we may request include, but is not limited to, your personal/company: email address, name, home address, and telephone number, credit card number, Tax ID, EIN, or Social Security Number. If you make a purchase, we may ask for your credit card number and billing information. We may also ask for other data to process your credit or financing request. Job applicants may be requested to provide information such as educational background, employment experience, and job interest. We may also collect information, such as your business or company information, age, gender, interests, preferences and favorites. Forms that you may fill in will indicate whether information requested is mandatory or voluntary. 

We may collect information about your visits to our websites, including the pages you view, the links, search terms you enter, and other actions you take in connection with the LinkTub.com website and services. We may also collect certain information from the browser you used to come to our website, such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type and language, access times, the Uniform Resource Locator (URL) of the website that referred you to our website and to which URL you browse away from our site if you click on a link on our site. 

In order to offer you a more consistent and personalized experience in your interactions with 2Hat Media, information collected through one source may be combined with information obtained through other 2Hat Media resources. We may also supplement the information we collect with information obtained from other parties.

Some 2Hat Media services may be co-branded and offered in conjunction with another company. If you register for, or use such services, both 2Hat Media and the other company may receive information collected in conjunction with the co-branded services, and may use the information according to each company's privacy statement and other agreements with you.

Some of these data points will be listed publicly (post login) to Advertisers using the LinkTub platform for building back links to their site. Here is a list of data points we use to help sell links to advertisers:   
Publicly Available Website (URL) data such as, but not limited to:   
• Number of Inbound Links to Your Site   
• Your Link Popularity Score   
• Meta Description / Meta Title   
• Page Rank   
• Domain Age   
• DMOZ Directory Listing (if available)   
• Yahoo! Directory Listing (if available) 

##### How You Can Access Your Information

2Hat Media wants to help you keep your personal information accurate. To view or edit your personal information that has been stored online in your LinkTub account, please visit your account sections of the Linktub.com.com website. For the security of your account, you will be required to sign in with your login ID and password.

##### How We Secure Your Personal Information

2Hat Media is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure, such as encryption, passwords, physical security, etc. While we strive to protect your personal information, 2Hat Media cannot ensure or warrant that the personal information or private communications you transmit to us will always remain private, and you do so at your own risk. 

If a password is used to help protect your accounts and personal information, it is your responsibility to keep your password confidential. Do not share this information with anyone. If you are sharing a computer with anyone you should always log out before leaving a site or service to protect access to your information from subsequent users. 

#####  Changes to Our Privacy Statement Regarding Customer and Online User Information 

We will occasionally update this privacy statement. If we make changes to the Privacy Statement Regarding Customer and Online User Information or make any material changes to how 2Hat Media will use your personal information, we will revise the Privacy Statement to reflect such changes and revise the statement's effective date, included at the end of this section. We encourage you to periodically review this statement to be informed of how 2Hat Media is protecting your personal information.

By accepting our “Privacy Policy / Terms of Use” you hold 2HatMedia, LinkTub.com, it affiliates and media partners harmless from any legal action against aforementioned parties.
